Guide to the Cornwall Miscellanea 1779-2003 MS 011 MS 011 MS 011
Cornwall Historical Society
- Photographic Materials
  - Negatives
    - Parades, October 1994, N.D. (Box 38, Folder 14)
      Photo negatives from Cornwall parades, including the one marking the town's 250th anniversary.
    - Miscellaneous, July 1994, N.D. (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Miscellaneous photo negatives, including post card images of Cornwall Bridge and West Cornwall, a milk ticket, and a car attributed to George Crosby.
    - Covered Bridges, N.D. (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Photo negatives of various New England covered bridges, including the bridge formally in Cornwall Bridge, and the covered bridge in West Cornwall.
    - Moser Sketch Book, January 4, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Color negatives from the sketch book of James Henry Moser taken at the home of Dody Prentice.
  - Tintypes
    - Oviatt, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Portrait of a young woman labeled as "Oviatt."
    - Camp Mohawk, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Tintype of Camp Mohawk.
    - Ford Family, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Tintypes of members of the Ford family.
    - Rogers Family, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Tintype of an unknown member of the Rogers family.
    - Smith Family, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 9)
      Tintypes of Cora Smith and Mary E. Smith.
    - Graves Family, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Tintype images of Cora Graves and two other unspecified members of her family.
    - Butcher Family, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 11)
      Tintype images of various unlabeled members of the Butcher family.
    - Unlabeled People, N.D. (Box 37, Folder 12)
      Tintypes of unspecified people.
- People
  - Woolsey Family
    - Edith Woolsey obituary, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - “Women’s Racing, 1940” in American Ski Annual by Elizabeth Woolsey, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - George Woolsey obituary, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Photo taken by Heathcote Muirson Woolsey at Edith Woolsey’s 75th birthday party, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Heathcote Muirson Woolsey obituary, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Jean Woolsey obituary, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Whitney Family
    - Judge Edward Baldwin Whitney memorial items, 1910-1911; , undated (Box 7, Folder 48-52)
    - Article on Josepha Whitney running for office, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Letter from Josepha Whitney to E.C. Starr, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Josiah West
    - Information on Josiah West sent to E.C. Starr, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Vail Family
    - Elizabeth Sedgwick Vaill publications, undated (Box 7, Folder 5-Jan)
    - Personal correspondence between Elizabeth S. Vaill and E.C. Starr, 1891-1897 (Box 7, Folder 8-Jun)
    - Elizabeth S. Vaill obituaries, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Marriage certificate of Herman L. Vaill and Flora Gold, 1823 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from D.C. Kilbourn, about Herman L. Vaill, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Photograph of Herman L. Vaill, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Joseph H. Vaill publications, 1890-1911; , undated (Box 7, Folder 13-34)
    - Personal correspondence between Joseph H. Vaill and E.C. Starr, 1896-1912 (Box 7, Folder 35-42)
    - Joseph H. Vaill obituaries, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 43-44)
    - Copies of The Aenid translated by Theodore F. Vaill, 1870, undated (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
  - Swift Family
    - Summons issued by Heman Swift, 1788 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Deed from Heman Swift to Samuel Bassett, 1792 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Letter sent from Heman Swift to Governor Huntington, 1795 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Receipt of Heman Swift from Lazarus Ives, 1800 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Heman Swift funeral sermon, 1815 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Items relating to Swift heirs requesting Heman Swift’s pension, 1856-1857 (Box 6, Folder 79-80)
    - Extract from Theodore Dwight’s Travels in New England, relating to Heman Swift, undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Mary E. Swift obituary, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Correspondence between E.C. Starr and William E. Swift, regarding family items, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 83-84)
  - Stone Family
    - Personal correspondence between E.C. Starr and Rev. John T. Stone, 1912-1915 (Box 6, Folder 62-63)
    - Evangelical Magazine article by Rev. Timothy Stone, regarding revival in Cornwall, 1812 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Funeral sermon for Heman Swift, delivered by Rev. Timothy Stone, 1815 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Sympathy letter sent by Rev. Timothy Stone to Jabez Swift, 1833 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Letter of recommendation written for seminary applicant Phebe Judson, by Rev. Timothy Stone, 1837 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - "Reading in Common Schools," by Professor Timothy D.P. Stone, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Connecticut School Journal article mentioning T.D.P. Stone, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence between John E. Calhoun and C.C. Carpenter, regarding Stone family information, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 70-71)
    - Notes on Stone genealogy, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Notes on Timothy Stone’s manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Squire Family
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr about the Squire-Wright family, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Smith Family
    - Letter from Almon E. Smith to unknown, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Receipt of Cornelia B. Smith, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Newspaper clippings regarding Cornelia B. Smith, 1914-1917 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Obituary, printed image, and signature of David L. Smith, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - "Centennial Hymn," by Fred Smith, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Biographical sketch of Fred Smith, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from S.J. Smith, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Marriage certificate of Chester Markham and Martha Day, written by Rev. Walter Smith, 1828 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - "Letter from the Coast," by Walter Dodge Smith, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Simmons Family
    - E.C. Starr correspondence regarding the Cornwall Simmons family, 1912-1913 (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
  - Sherwood Family
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr, regarding Hannah Sherwood, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Pratt Family
    - David Pratt deeds, 1800 (Box 6, Folder 25-27)
    - Ezra D. Pratt deeds, 1832-1877 (Box 6, Folder 28-32)
    - Miner Pratt deeds, 1795-1834 (Box 6, Folder 33-40)
    - Miner Pratt receipts, 1815-1832 (Box 6, Folder 41-43)
    - Empty deed holders of Miner and E.D. Pratt, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Miner Pratt probate documents, 1832-1846 (Box 6, Folder 45-47)
    - Excerpt from Rev. F.W. Chapman’s Pratt genealogy, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Porter Family
    - Sermons of Ebenezer Porter, 1811-1818 (Box 6, Folder 14-17)
    - Publications mentioning Ebenezer Porter, 1912; , undated (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
    - Letter sent from Lucy Pierce Porter to Joshua Pierce, asking him to sponsor Andover Seminary student, 1817 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence of E.C. Starr, regarding Vermont Supreme Court Judge Thomas Porter, 1892-1895 (Box 6, Folder 21-23)
    - Article on Thomas Porter in, The Green Bag, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pettibone Family
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr by Benjamin W. Pettibone, regarding the Welch family, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Genealogical sketch of the Pierce family, by Benjamin W. Pettibone, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - List of Cornwall students who attended Amherst College compiled by B.W. Pettibone, undated (Box 6, Folder 10-Sep)
    - Excerpt from sermon preached by Rev. Ira Pettibone, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Rev. Ira Pettibone to Cornwall church clerk, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Colonel Ira W. Pettibone obituary, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Payne Family
    - Article on Cold Harbor Cemetery, by Joseph Payne, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Notes on the genealogy of the Cornwall Paynes, by Oliver N. Payne, Esq., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Commission of Rufus Payne, Jr. as a captain in Conn. Militia, 1828 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Millard Family
    - Contracts made by M.J. Millard, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr by Helen W. Reynolds, about the Millard family, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Frank V.A. Loucks
    - Photograph, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lewis Family
    - Newspaper story on proposed Mayor Henry G. Lewis statue, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Henry G. Lewis memorial items, 1892-1895; , undated (Box 5, Folder 51-54)
    - Correspondence between E.C. Starr and G.H. Ford, regarding donation of Lewis family items, 1900-1923 (Box 5, Folder 55-56)
    - Items donated to E.C. Starr, belonging to H.G. Lewis’ father William, 1803-1811 (Box 5, Folder 57-59)
    - Genealogy of the Cornwall Lewis family, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Johnson Family
    - Letter sent to Ebert Johnson from sister, Lill Green, 1843 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Collection of Johnson family history items, 1917-1940; , undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Jerome Family
    - Article, "Chauncey Jerome on Summerless Year", 1931 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Jerome family history sent to E.C. Starr, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Ives Family
    - Correspondence between Harlan Ives and E.C. Starr, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 41-42)
    - Letter and prescription sent to E.C. Starr from Dr. John W. Ives, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from Joseph B. Ives, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Notes on Ives genealogy, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hubbard Family
    - Autograph postcards from Mrs. L.M.B. Hubbard to E.C. Starr, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Autograph letters from William Brewster Hubbard to E.C. Starr, 1906; , undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - William B. Hubbard letter regarding his purchase of Chauncey E. Baldwin Insurance Co., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - William B. Hubbard obituary, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Hubbard-Gold-Beers genealogical chart, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Hollister Family
    - Correspondence between E.C. Starr and Hollister descendants, about Cornwall ancestors, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - Notes on the Hollister genealogy, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Hill Family
    - Copy of letter sent to John R. Hill from Aaron S. Hill, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Autograph letter from Rowland Hill to E.C. Starr, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Rowland Hill newspaper clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hart Family
    - Postcard sent to E.C. Starr from Albert J. Hart, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from George H. Greene, about Alvin N. Hart, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Family records of Charles E. Hart, 1831-1909 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Charles E. Hart personal correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - War correspondence from Charles E. Hart to friend Clarence, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "A Biographical Sketch of George Spencer Hart", 1904 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - John Clark Hart sermon and lecture transcriptions, undated (Box 5, Folder 21-22)
    - John C. Hart memorial items, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - John Milton Hart obituary, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - “The Lord’s Prayer” sheet music by N.R. Hart, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Marriage certificate of Seely Hart and Jennette Seelye, 1854 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Butter book of Seelye Hart, 1861-1913 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Travel journal and account book of Seelye Hart, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Sarah C. Hart correspondence with E.C. Starr, regarding John C. Hart, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Harrison Family
    - Letter sent from Chandler Harrison to his brother Noah, 1821 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - George C. Harrison funeral booklet, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - George C. Harrison obituary, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - John Harrison receipt from Jesse Hotchkiss, 1835 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Account of J.R. Harrison with town of Cornwall, 1836 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Ralph Calhoun Harrison biographical sketch, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ralph C. Harrison memorial items, 1918; , undated (Box 5, Folder 13-Oct)
    - Genealogical notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Harris Family
    - Genealogical papers, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Letter sent from Henry Harris to E.C. Starr, regarding David Harris, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Biographical account of Israel Harris, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Gold Family
    - Published text of Sarah Gold’s funeral sermon, 1766 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Complaint of David Dibble against Hezekiah Gold, for breach of the peace, 1766 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Edward F. Gold deeds, 1854-1869 (Box 4, Folder 37-40)
    - Edward F. Gold fire insurance policies, 1863-1866 (Box 4, Folder 41-43)
    - Edward F. Gold probate documents, 1869-1870 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - “Descriptive Notice” of Stephen J. Gold’s heating apparatus, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence between Theodore S. Gold and the Gaylord family, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Story about, and article by, George R. Gold in The Wolverine Citizen, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Mention of paper by George R. Gold in The Plymouth Weekly, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr by George R. Gold, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Published tributes to George R. Gold, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from George R. Gold, about visit to Cherokee Country and Boudinot grave, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Letter from Samuel F. Gold to unnamed Cornwall cousin, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Article in Domestic Engineering on Samuel F. Gold, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence between E.C. Starr and James Douglas Gold, regarding music appropriation, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 54-55)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr about information on Thomas R. Gold, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Clipping about Harriet Gold Boudinot descendants, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Edward E. Gold obituary, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Newspaper article on the history of the Cornwall Gold family, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Photograph of Charles L. Gold and J.D. Gold, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Mrs. Edward M. Foote
    - Personal correspondence, 1908-1953 (Box 4, Folder 27-32)
    - Letter from Mrs. Edward M. Foote, to be opened upon her death, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Information on well drilling at the Foote property, "Hull House", 1948 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Farnsworth Family
    - Letter sent to Jane Farnsworth from E. Goodell, 1848 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence between Jane Farnsworth and Mary Farnsworth, 1850-1852 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
    - Personal correspondence between Jane Farnsworth and L. Haywood, 1850-1851 (Box 4, Folder 19-22)
    - Letter sent to Jane Farnsworth from U.B. Wilder, 1851 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Letter sent to Jane Farnsworth from M. Warner, describing a trip to the Deep South, 1851 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Letter sent to Jane Farnsworth from Louisa, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Letter sent to Mrs. Emily Farnsworth, from J.G. Farnsworth, 1854 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Everest Family
    - Will of Eunice Everest, 1837 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Sketch of Dr. Solomon Everest, by Haynes Lord Everest, Jr., 1901 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dean Family
    - Correspondence between B.S. Dean and E.C. Starr, 1901-1912 (Box 4, Folder 2-Jan)
    - Correspondence between J.E. Dean and E.C. Starr, 1928-1930 (Box 4, Folder 4-Mar)
    - "A Short History of the William Dean Family"by B.S. Dean and J.E. Dean, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Supplement to the Dean History", 1910 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dean genealogy from Dr. Thomas Dean, immigrant ancestor from England, by J.E. Dean, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Carter-Bates-Bennet-Dean Lines," by J. Everest Dean, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Genealogy of the descendants of Reuben Dean (1701-1790), undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Photograph of Dean house interior, Cornwall Bridge, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Photograph of the chimney of the Dean house, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Photograph of Ruth Dean’s church membership transfer letter, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Photograph of Dean family graves in Ohio, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Curtiss Family
    - "Anniversary Hymn," by Lucy Sackett Curtiss, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Letter from William C. Curtiss to E.C. Starr, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Newspaper clipping, "Dr. Curtiss is Fined $100", 1909 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Obituary of William M. Curtiss, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Corban Family
    - The Hotchkiss Literary Monthly and Alumni Bulletin, mentioning Ralph E. Corban, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Letter from Ralph E. Corban to E.C. Starr, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Photograph of Frank W. Corban, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Complaint against Jonathan Curtis for Sabbath-breaking and swearing, 1800 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Letter from M.M. Curtis to E.C. Starr, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Letter from G.C. Sullivan to E.C. Starr, regarding death of her father, Civil War veteran Levi Curtis, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cole Family
    - The Cornwall Star Vol. II, No. 16, edited by its proprietor, Edwin D. Cole, 1881 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Article, "Printer’s Ink," by Henry H. Cole, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Roslindale Congregational Church booklet, mentioning Henry H. Cole, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Letter from Henry H. Cole to E.C. Starr, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Clarke Family
    - Genealogical letter sent from F.D. Clarke to E.C. Starr, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Memorial sermon for Benjamin Sedgwick, preached by Rev. William Barton Clarke, 1857 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Text of memorial address given by William Barton Clarke in memory of Rev. Thomas L. Shipman, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Memorial sketch of Mrs. Catherine R. Rogers by William Barton Clarke, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence between William Barton Clarke and E.C. Starr, 1892-1893 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Advertisement for A More Excellent Way, by William Barton Clarke, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Clark Family
    - Andrew M. Clark obituary, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Letter sent from Charlotte E. Clark, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Letter sent from Ernest D. Clark to E.C. Starr, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Marriage notice for Ernest D. Clark and Bertha Branch, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Newspaper story, "100,000 Acres in Massanutten Wanted," mentioning Ernest D. Clark, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Letter sent from Loyal B. Clark to E.C. Starr, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Letter sent from William D. Bosler to E.C. Starr, regarding New York mayor Aaron Clark, and possible Cornwall connections, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Genealogy of William Clark, of Clark Hill, Cornwall, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - William Chidester
    - Clipping of emigrating from Connecticut to Ohio, 1805 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Chandler Family
    - Correspondence between Mrs. Samuel Shannon and E.C. Starr, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
  - Edward D. Cartwright
    - Tax receipts, 1919-1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Carter Family
    - E.C. Starr correspondence with Carter descendants, regarding Cornwall Carters, 1898-1905 (Box 3, Folder 15-22)
    - Michael Gannett correspondence with Arthur Francis Carter and Jon Tandy, about Cornwall Carters, 1989-2001 (Box 3, Folder 23-25)
    - Manuscript, "Brother Lost," by Arthur Francis Carter, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Connecticut Western News two-part story on Carter family, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
    - Photograph of Thomas G. Carter, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Photograph of "Devils’ Tower," Wyoming, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Photograph of Theodore George Carter, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - "Carter House Views" series of photographs, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Photograph of Charles David Carter, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Photograph of Jonathan R. Carter, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Photograph of T.J. Carter and Reuben Tyner, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Photograph of Judge Benjamin Winston Carter, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Photograph of Serena Guy Carter, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Photograph of Serena Parrott McSpadden, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Photograph of Thomas Jefferson Carter, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Photograph of Thomas Jefferson Carter, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Calhoun Family
    - Poetry referencing Cornwall, sent to John Calhoun from Grace Miner Lippincott, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 9-Aug)
    - Issues of Congregational Connecticut belonging to John Calhoun, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 11-Oct)
    - Letter sent to Sarah C. Calhoun from William F. Kellogg, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Account of the Robinson family, by descendant Sarah C. Calhoun, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Notes on Calhoun genealogy by Sarah C. Calhoun, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Burton Family
    - Newspaper clipping about Memorial Day address given by Capt. Henry E. Burton, 1874 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "A Memorial of Robert H. Gillette," by Nathanial Judson Burton, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from Nathanial J. Burton, 1880 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings about Nathaniel J. Burton, 1892-1903 (Box 3, Folder 6-May)
    - Letter sent by Rachel C. Burton to E.C. Starr, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bunnell Family
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from Ada Bunnell, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brewster Family
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from Carrier A. Brewster, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Biographical sketch of Edward Everett Brewster, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Bradford Family
    - Schoolbooks published by the American Tract Society belonging to Edmund Bradford, 1859; , undated (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
    - Essay by Mary E. Bradford, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Circular of the Bradford Union Association, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bonney Family
    - Stephen Bonney’s commission as a major in the Conn. Militia, 1817 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Notes between Polly Bonney and Seth Pierce, 1828-1830 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Materials related to the final expenses of Polly Bonney, 1830-1831 (Box 2, Folder 26-30)
    - Washington Insurance Company policy of Stephen Bonney, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence between J.H. Bonney and administrators at the Vermont Asylum for the Insane, about his brother, 1866-1873 (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
    - Circular letters sent to J.H. Bonney from abolitionist educator Jerusha M. Skinner, 1870-1871 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Letter sent to Mrs. Irene Bonney from Stephen Bonney, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Letter sent to Mrs. Irene Bonney from Marietta, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Letter sent to John H. Bonney from Julie and Louise, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Letter sent to John H. Bonney from John R. Harrison, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Letter sent to Abbey Bonney from Mary Ann Bonney, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Letter sent to Abbey Bonney from Mary Bonney, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Letter sent to J.H. Bonney from William Bonney, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Empty envelope addressed to J.H. Bonney, with stamps, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Letter sent to Mrs. Stephen Bonney from Walter and Louise, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Blinn Family
    - Letters sent to E.C. Starr from Bertha Blinn Johnson, about the Blinn family, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Birdseye Family
    - "Remarks of Mr. Birdseye, New York, The Bankrupt Bill", 1841 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence between Victory Birdseye and son, Lucien Birdseye, 1852-1853 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - "Biographical Sketches of Victory and Lucian Birdseye", 1883 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence between Lucien Birdseye and E.C. Starr, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - "The Record of Ebenezer Birdseye’s Family", undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Benedict Family
    - Genealogy of Edwin Benedict, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Letter from Edwin Benedict sent to E.C. Starr, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)